{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "たいへん（な）",
      "answer": "difficult, hard; terrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "ちいさな",
      "answer": "small; little"
    },
    {
      "question": "にぎやか（な）",
      "answer": "bustling; busy(for places)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ねっしん",
      "answer": "enthusiastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハッピー（な）",
      "answer": "happy"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハンサム（な）",
      "answer": "handsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひつよう（な）",
      "answer": "necessary"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひま（な）",
      "answer": "free, spare(time)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ふくざつ（な）",
      "answer": "complex, complicated"
    },
    {
      "question": "ふしぎ（な）",
      "answer": "mysterious; curious"
    },
    {
      "question": "ふしんせつ（な）",
      "answer": "unkind; unfriendly"
    },
    {
      "question": "ふべん（な）",
      "answer": "inconvenient"
    },
    {
      "question": "へた（な）",
      "answer": "unskillful; poor"
    },
    {
      "question": "へん（な）",
      "answer": "strange, weird, odd; funny, eccentric"
    },
    {
      "question": "べんり（な）",
      "answer": "convenient; handy; useful"
    },
    {
      "question": "まじめ（な）",
      "answer": "serious; deligent"
    },
    {
      "question": "まっくろ（な）",
      "answer": "pitch black"
    },
    {
      "question": "まっしろ（な）",
      "answer": "pure white"
    },
    {
      "question": "むくち（な）",
      "answer": "silent; reticent"
    },
    {
      "question": "むめい（な）",
      "answer": "anonymous; nameless"
    },
    {
      "question": "むり（な）",
      "answer": "impossible;  unreasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゆうめい（な）",
      "answer": "famous"
    },
    {
      "question": "らく（な）",
      "answer": "comfortable; easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "りっぱ（な）",
      "answer": "fine; splendid; gorgeous"
    }
  ]
}
